Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Carey Investigation Files, Series 15; 1.5 Linear Feet
  - New Jersey/Carey Fundraiser, 1997 October; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Scandal- Local Unions, 1997; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - National Legal and Policy Center, Undated; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Carey and 'Pot', 1997; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Thompson Committee, 1997-1998; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - January 1997, 1997 January; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - March 1997, 1997 March; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - April 1997, 1997 April; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - May 1997, 1997 May; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - June 1997, 1997 June; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - June 1997 Davis Arrested, 1997 June; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - July 1997, 1997 July; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - August 1997, 1997 August; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - August 1997, 1997 August; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - August 1997 Quindel Summary, 1997 August; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - September 1997, 1997 September; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 26)
  - September 1997, 1997 September; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 27)
  - September 1997 Ansara, Nash, Davis Plead Guilty, 1997 September; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 28)
  - September 1997 Carey Disqualified, 1997 September; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 29)
  - September 1997 Carey Disqualified, 1997 September; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 30)
  - October 1997, 1997 October; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 31)
  - October 1997 Nash Pleads Guilty, 1997 October; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 32)
  - Election Appeals Cases- Exhibits, 1997 September 22; Series 15 (Box 121, Folder 33)
  - Hamilton Memo's, 1995-1997; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - November 1997, 1997 November; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - November 1997 Carey- IRB Charges, 1997 November 25; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - November 1997 Conboy Disqualifies Carey, 1997 November 17; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - November 1997 IRB Charges Carey, 1997 November; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - December 1997, 1997 December; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - January 1998 Carey and the IRB, 1998 January; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - March 1998 Nash/Carey IRB, 1998 March; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - October 1997 Hamilton IRB Charges, 1997 October; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - March 1998 Nash Memo, 1998 March; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - April 1997 Nash Before Edelstein, 1997 April 17; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - July 1998 Carey Expelled, 1998 July; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - August 1998- Blitz Guilty, 1998 August; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - October 1998 Charny Pleads Guilty, 1998 October; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - February 1999- Nash Lied, 1999 February; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Scandal- 1998, Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Scandal- 1999, Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Scandal- 2000, Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Scandal- 2001, Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Carey- Explusion Upheld, 2001 April 23; Series 15 (Box 122, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Research Files, 1996-2004; Series 16; 1.5 Linear Feet
  This series is a collection of articles and other documents on a range of topics pertaining to the IBT.
  This series is arranged by topic.
  - Detroit News/Labor Day Rally, Detroit 1997, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Detroit News Rally 1997, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts- 2003 Hoffa, 2003 May 20; Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - 2001- Labor Day- Briefing Book, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa Detroit Economic Club 2004, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - State of Union- 2001, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - State of Union National Press Club 2000, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - 1998 Vote Count Holiday Inn- Alexandria, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - 1998 News Articles, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - 1998- Hoffa to Deaner, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - 1997- Hoffa in Harrisburg, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - 1998 Re-run, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - 1996 IBT Convention Philadelphia, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - 1996 IBT Convention Philadelphia, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - 1996 Convention, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - 1996 Convention, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Permanent Normal Trade Relations (PNTR) 2000, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - PNTR 2000, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - PNTR Demonstrations- April 2000, 2000 April; Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - PNTR Demonstrations- April 2000, 2000 April; Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - PNTR Demonstrations- April 2000, 2000 April; Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - PNTR- April 2000, 2000 April; Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - PNTR 2000, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - World Trade Organization (WTO) 1999, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - 1999- WTO, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - WTO- Seattle 1999, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - WTO- Seattle 1999, Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - WTO Seattle, 1999; Series 16 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - 2002- Dues Increase, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - 2002- Dues Increase, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - 1994- IBT Dues Increase, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - 2002- Dues Increase, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - 1994 Dues Increase- TDU, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - IBT Constitution, 2001 June; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Delegates, 2002 April 17; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Local Union Letters, 2002 April; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Teamster Magazine, 2002 May-June; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Delegate Report, Undated; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Member Poll, 2002 April 25; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Local Union Letters, 2002 April; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa Agenda, 2002 April-May; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Video Script, 2002 March 19; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Deaner- Special Convention, 2002 March 7; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Strike Fund Posters, 2002-2003; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Constitution Committee, 2002 April 26; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Drafts- Blue Ribbon Report, 2002 March 1; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Why A Special Convention?, 2002 March 6; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - TDU Lies, 2002; Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - 2000- King Memorial, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - State of Union Teamsters 2000, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - 2001- Hoffa Honored By Bay Area Labor Union Party, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - September 11, 2001, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - 2001- Hoffa Detroit News Interview, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - DC Friends of Ireland- Hoffa 2004, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - 1999- Teamster National Black Caucus, Series 16 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - 2001 Hoffa Briefing Book National Press Club, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Unity Conference 2003- Joint Councils, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - PA Conference Meeting- 2001, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Las Vegas Magazine Interview 2001, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - 2001- Imperfect Union American Prospect, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa Press 2001, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - 2001- Irish American Labor Coalition, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - 1998- Hoffa Website Crew, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - 2002 New Republic, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - 2003- PA Conference, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Jim Hoffa- Interviews 1998/1999, Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Record 2002 Special Convention, 2002 April 30; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Trade Division Resolutions, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Trade Division Newsletters, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Trade Division Newsletters, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - UPS Caravan, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Local Union Letters, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Frequently Asked Questions, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Public Employees, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission, 2002; Series 16 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - News Articles, 2002; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Research, Undated; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - TDU, 2002; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Anti-TDU Flyers, 2002; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Meetings and Agenda, 2002; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - PowerPoint Presentation, 2002 February; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission Report, 2002 March 1; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Constitution Committee, 2001 June 29; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Deaner Research, Undated; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Delegate Seating, 2002 April 30; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Teamster Leader, 2002 April; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Delegate Handouts- Convention, 2002 April 30; Series 16 (Box 126, Folder 12)
- Notes and Subject Binders, 1972-2014; Series 17
  This series is a set odf 3-ring binders that document Leo Deaner's work activitiesin the James P. Hoffa administration as well as general IBT operations.
  Binders in this series are arranged chronologically or by subject.
  - Executive Assistant to GP, 1999-2010; Series 17 Subseries 1
    - LD Memos to JPH, 1999-2002; Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Binder 1)
    - LD Memos to JPH, 2002-2003; Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Binder 2)
    - LD Memos to JPH, 2004-2006; Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Binder 3)
    - LD Memos to JPH, 2007-2011; Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Binder 1)
    - LD Memos to JPH, 2011-2012; Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Binder 2)
    - LD Memos to JPH, 2013-2014; Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Binder 3)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; February 12 & 14, 2008, Washington D.C., Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 129, Binder 1)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; May 16 & 17, 2008 Las Vegas, Nevada, Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 129, Binder 2)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; September 9 & 10, 2008, Hollywood, Florida, Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 129, Binder 3)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; December 8, 2008, Teleconference, Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 130, Binder 1)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; January 19, 2009, Washington D.C., Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 130, Binder 2)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; September 22-24, 2009, Asheville, North Carolina, Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 130, Binder 3)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Assistant to GP; May 1 & 2, 2009, Las Vegas, Nevada, Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 131, Binder 1)
    - Leo Deaner-Executive Secretary to the General President; May 7-8, 2010, Las Vegas Nevada, Series 17 Subseries 1 (Box 131, Binder 2)
  - Notes, 1999-2014; Series 17 Subseries 2
    - Notes 1999, 2000, 2001, 1999-2001; Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 153, Binder 1)
    - Notes 2001-2002, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Binder 1)
    - Notes 2002/2003, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Binder 2)
    - Notes 2003, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Binder 3)
    - Notes 2004, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Binder 4)
    - Notes 2004, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Binder 1)
    - Notes 2004-2005, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Binder 2)
    - Notes 2005, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Binder 3)
    - Notes 2005, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Binder 1)
    - Notes 2006 through October, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Binder 2)
    - Notes 2006, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Binder 3)
    - Notes 2006, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 134, Binder 4)
    - Notes 2006, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Binder 1)
    - Notes 2006 through December, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Binder 2)
    - Notes January 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Binder 3)
    - Notes February 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Binder 4)
    - Notes March 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Binder 1)
    - Notes April 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Binder 2)
    - Notes May 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Binder 3)
    - Notes June 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Binder 4)
    - Notes July 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Binder 1)
    - Notes August 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Binder 2)
    - Notes September 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Binder 3)
    - Notes October 2007, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Binder 4)
    - Notes November 2007, September 2007; Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Binder 1)
    - Notes January 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Binder 2)
    - Notes February 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Binder 3)
    - Notes March 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Binder 4)
    - Notes April 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Binder 1)
    - Notes June 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Binder 2)
    - Notes July 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Binder 3)
    - Notes August 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Binder 4)
    - Notes August 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Binder 1)
    - Notes September 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Binder 2)
    - Notes September 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Binder 3)
    - Notes October 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Binder 4)
    - Notes November 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 156, Binder 4)
    - Notes December 2008, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Binder 1)
    - Notes January 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Binder 2)
    - Notes February 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Binder 3)
    - Notes February/March 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Binder 4)
    - Notes March 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Binder 1)
    - Notes April 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Binder 2)
    - Notes May 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Binder 3)
    - Notes May/June/July 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Binder 4)
    - Notes September/October 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Binder 2)
    - Notes October/November 2009, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Binder 3)
    - Notes December 2009-January 2010, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Binder 4)
    - Notes January, February, March 2010, January-July 2010; Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Binder 1)
    - Notes April 2010, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Binder 2)
    - Notes May/June 2010, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Binder 3)
    - Notes June/July 2010, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Binder 4)
    - Notes August-September 2010, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Binder 1)
    - Notes October-December 2010, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Binder 2)
    - Notes December/January 2010-2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Binder 1)
    - Notes January 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Binder 3)
    - Notes February 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Binder 4)
    - Notes March/April 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Binder 5)
    - Notes May 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Binder 6)
    - Notes July 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Binder 2)
    - Notes August 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Binder 3)
    - Notes September 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Binder 4)
    - Notes October/November 2011, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Binder 1)
    - Notes Jan/Feb/Mar 2012, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Binder 2)
    - Notes March/April/May/June 2012, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Binder 3)
    - Notes July/August 2012, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Binder 4)
    - Notes September/October 2012, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Binder 5)
    - Notes September/October 2012, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 1)
    - Notes Nov/Dec 2012, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 1)
    - Notes January 2012, January 2013; Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 2)
    - Notes February 2013, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 3)
    - Notes March/April 2013, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 4)
    - Notes May-July 2013, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 5)
    - Notes July-August 2013, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Binder 6)
    - Notes August/September 2013, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Binder 1)
    - Notes October 2013, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Binder 2)
    - Notes Nov/Dec 2013-January 2014, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Binder 3)
    - Notes February/March/April 2014, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Binder 4)
    - Notes May/June 2014, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Binder 1)
    - Notes July/August 2014, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Binder 2)
    - Notes September 2014, Series 17 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Binder 3)
  - Subjects, 1972-2011; Series 17 Subseries 3
    - "Teamsters Fighting for the Future"-25th International Convention, July 15-19, 1996, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 151, Binder 1)
    - "Teamsters Safety and Health Manual 1972", Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 151, Binder 2)
    - IBT No Raid Mutual Aid Pacts", July 1, 1975; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 151, Binder 3)
    - "Teamsters Workshop Session # 16 June 25-29, 1979", Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 151, Binder 4)
    - "A Well Informed Membership is Our Best Security: Teamsters Leadership Academy", Summer 2009; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 151, Binder 5)
    - IBT Core Employment Policies Employee Handbook, 2003; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 153, Binder 2)
    - YRCW Concessions 2008/2009, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 153, Binder 3)
    - YRCW Concessions 2008/2009, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 153, Binder 4)
    - Carhaul, 1999-2006; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 154, Binder 1)
    - Freight, 2002-2006; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 154, Binder 2)
    - IBT Division Airline-UAL, 2003-2008; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 154, Binder 3)
    - YRC Contract Adjustment, 2008-2009; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 154, Binder 4)
    - Expense Reports, 2000-2003; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 155, Binder 1)
    - Expense Reports, 2004-2006; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 155, Binder 2)
    - International Representatives, Department and Division Staff, January 2005; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 155, Binder 3)
    - Expenses, 2007-2009; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 155, Binder 4)
    - Directors Meetings, 2001-2003; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 157, Binder 1)
    - Directors Meetings, 2004-2007; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 157, Binder 2)
    - Directors Meetings, 2008-2009; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 157, Binder 3)
    - Rabin Dinner Trip to Israel, 2008; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 158, Binder 1)
    - Rabin Dinner Trip to Israel, 2008; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 158, Binder 2)
    - Rabin Dinner to Israel, 2008; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 158, Binder 3)
    - ABF 2010, 2009-2010; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Binder 1)
    - ABF 2010 Teamster Response to Lawsuit, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Binder 2)
    - YRC 2010, 2009-2010; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Binder 3)
    - YRC 2010, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Binder 4)
    - YRC 2011, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Binder 5)
    - Carhaul, 2009-2010; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 160, Binder 1)
    - IBT Convention 2011, 2010-2011; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 160, Binder 2)
    - IBT Convention 2011, 2010-2011; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 160, Binder 3)
    - IBT 2011Convention Committees, 2010-2011; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 160, Binder 4)
    - 2011 Unity Meetings JRH Dinner Organizer's Meeting, 2010-2011; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 160, Binder 5)
    - Expenses 2010, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 161, Binder 1)
    - Carhaul 2010/2011, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 161, Binder 2)
    - IBT Election 2011, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 161, Binder 3)
    - CUE Local 2010, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 161, Binder 4)
    - UPS Contract 2013/2014, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 161, Binder 5)
    - TDU AND IS, 2011; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 162, Binder 1)
    - Freight 2010/2011/2012, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 162, Binder 2)
    - Freight 2012/2013, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 162, Binder 3)
    - UPS Freight & Others Contract 2013/2014, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 162, Binder 4)
    - Freight 2014, Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 162, Binder 5)
    - Teamsters: Changing to Grow: IBT Trade Division and Conference Strategic Plans, 2004; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 156, Binder 1)
    - DRIVE Department of Field Action: Meeting of General Executive Board, March 26-30, 2007; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 156, Binder 2)
    - "IBT Document Scan Retrieval project-Databank IMX Analysis Deliverables and Recommendation-November 6, 2007", Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 156, Binder 3)
    - LRA Consulting-"Planning for the Future" Correspondence & Accounting, 2001-2007; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 152, Binder 1)
    - "Securing the Future: A Financial Analysis of the Pre-and Post-Special Convention Periods and Recommendations for Increasing Organizing Funding", June 15, 2007; Series 17 Subseries 3 (Box 152, Binder 2)
- James P. Hoffa, 1991-2008; Series 18; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Conents of this series are primarily arranged chronologically.
  The main focus of this series is James P. Hoffa's terms in office and his on going restructuring plans for the Teamsters. Also included are documents and photos on Hoffa Jr.'s campaigns from 1991 - 2001.
  - Campaigns, 1991 - 2001; Subseries 1; .5 Linear Feet
    This subseries is organized chronologically.
    This subseries includes campaign promotional material, campaign trail photobraphs, anti-opponent flyers, and campaign talking points.
    - Hoffa Campaign for IBT Convention "Let Hoffa Run for IBT General President!", 1991; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 1)
    - James P. Hoffa Addresses Steelton Rally - Bid for Votes, 1996; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Hoffa '96 NYC HQ, 1996; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Hoffagrams by Deaner, 1997-1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Hoffa - Left Media, 1998-1999; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Anti-Morris Flyers Done by Deaner, Mike Clark and Deaner JC 53 Coordinators, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Anti-Mims Flyers done by Deaner, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Padellaro Flyers done by Deaner, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Attack Leaflets written by L. Deaner against Morris, 1996; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Flyers done by Deaner Against Metz, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Hoffa Flyers done by Deaner, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Hoffa national Flyers by Deaner, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Flyers Done by Deaner for Desanti Region VP Campaign, 1998; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Hoffa Talking Points, 2001; Series 18 (Box Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Restructuring and Finances, 2002-2008; Series 19; .5 Linear Feet
    This subseries is arranged first by finances and then restructuring projects. These ar ethen arranged chronologically.
    Documents included in this subseries are financial overviews, printouts of restructuring presentations, and correspondence regarding program changes.
    - Special Convention - Final Report of the Blue Ribbon Commission on Teamster Finances, 2002; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Strike and Defense Fund - Revenue and Expenses Report, 2007-2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - LRA Consulting Memos - "State of Finances", 2007-2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Teamster Growth Ideas, 2007-2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - IBT Finances - Report of the General Treasurer, 2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Finances - "Agenda for Growth" Presentation, January 2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Finances - "Change to Win", February 2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - "Establishing a Legacy of Growth" and "Financing IBT Growth" Presentations, March 2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - "Financing IBT Growth" Talking Points and Presentation, July 2008; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Restructuring - Department of Education, 2005; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 10)